♪Listen to the cicadas in the midsummer♪
♪The reflection in your eyes♪
♪A brilliant scenery♪
♪Moonlight spills over
the endless clear sky♪
♪The roar of the heartbeat
leaves a trace behind♪
♪Crush, when night meets dawn♪
♪Crush, rushing to you in the crowd♪
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
♪Fervent, boiling love♪
♪How you long for the future♪
♪Charging recklessly, getting hurt♪
♪Fall in my heart♪
♪If tears fill your eyes♪
♪Let the damp wind stay in memories♪
♪We stand by each other among the crowd♪
=Be Passionately in Love=
=Episode 15=
(We'll Meet as We Expected)
(Send Waitlist Admission File)
It's a confession.
Look.
A guy is confessing downstairs.
He's so brave.
Come on. I can't believe
he will confess with flowers
and a loudspeaker.
So corny.
What?
Xu Zhi.
Look.
A guy is confessing, holding flowers.
It's so outdated.
What's worse, it's a moral abduction.
It's fine
if the boy and girl like each other.
If the girl doesn't like the boy,
she'll be put on the spot.
It's so awkward.
If I were the girl,
I'd be so embarrassed.
I can't stand it.
Xu Zhi, the Architecture freshman,
I'm a Humanities student.
Xu Zhi.
Let me see.
Turns out the girl
he's confessing to is you.
Right now,
I want to use a poem
to express my feelings for you.
A poem.
I am
a desperate person.
Come back.
Alright, stop looking.
Get inside.
Wait a moment.
I'm grabbing my clothes.
I remember what you looked last fall.
Sorry.
A gray beret.
Si, I'm going down.
Hello, Dad.
Hello, Zhi.
How's your leg?
Much better.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
If it hurts again, don't ignore it.
You must go to the hospital
for a check-up.
On the barren land of mine,
you are my last rose.
Whose voice is that?
Pretty loud, huh?
A new suitor?
Is he handsome?
Which department?
I don't know or care.
Besides, can he be
as handsome as Chen Luzhou?
Why compare the new guy with him?
Get a new one.
No, I don't.
As a student of the Chinese department,
he's reciting
someone else's poems.
Not every place has romantic poets.
That's right.
Young people now
can't write better poetry
than those in my day.
You know what?
Mr. Fu was once a renowned poet
in our city.
Although I don't know
whether he wrote those poems
or copied someone else's,
he certainly enchanted
a lot of artistic young women.
You mean after Chen Luzhou gets old,
he will be like Mr. Fu?
It's possible.
Then I should seriously
find a new boyfriend here.
I'll keep my options open.
Here you go.
If you think that way,
I'll feel relieved.
Alright, I'm hanging up.
Okay then.
For you,
I sing.
Enough.
Stop shouting.
I am Xu Zhi's roommate.
You like Xu Zhi?
So far,
there have been some guys
pursuing Xu Zhi.
Listen.
You go back.
I'll get you in line.
How about No. 8?
Waiting in line?
Wait, it depends on feelings.
It's all about fate,
not who comes first.
You are quite confident.
Have you heard of Jiang Yu?
The sophomore
from the philosophy department...
The hottest guy
in the Humanities Academy.
He's in line too.
Alright.
Stop it and go.
Get out of here.
He's leaving?
In our school,
there are three boys to one girl.
It's out of proportion.
Girls like you are definitely
in high demand.
Please.
But don't think of
that loudspeaker guy.
What about Jiang Yu?
Do you like him?
No, absolutely not.
I don't have any feelings for him.
Besides, I don't want to date now.
What did I miss?
Hey.
Don't you think
Jiang Yu and Xu Zhi make a great couple?
- And he's so handsome.
- Yes.
I really have no feelings for him.
Besides, I don't want to date now.
Tell me.
Do you already like someone
secretly?
I dated someone
after high school graduation.
But we broke up some time ago.
Now, I'm focused on my studies
to serve my country.
These are my boyfriends
for the next four years.
What?
You dated before?
Oh my, what kind of guy was he?
Tell us about him.
I'm so curious.
What kind of person can
win you over?
A super hot guy.
- A hot guy?
That's it?
It's actually very subjective
to judge a person's looks.
For example,
I really think
Jiang Yu is handsome.
But you don't think so.
Moreover,
beauty is in the eye of the beholder.
Maybe her ex-boyfriend
isn't handsome at all.
Then, there's nothing I can say.
It could be my personal problem.
In my opinion, in today's world,
bad guys are everywhere.
Especially handsome guys.
But I think
Jiang Yu is very reliable.
- I know.
- Yeah.
Really.
You should try hanging out with him.
He's a good singer.
How romantic.
I know!
How romantic is he?
Like swinging on a toilet seat?
I didn't expect this from you, Xu Zhi.
(Free this Sunday, Artist?)
I asked for you,
and he said yes.
Swinging on a toilet seat.
Jiang Yu's free this weekend.
Let's not.
It's quite difficult.
I think it's okay.
Alright, let's wash up.
These past two months,
I've eaten with you guys quite a lot.
Both you and Lucy aren't here now,
so it's my first time
having a meal alone with Zhi.
It feels a bit strange.
Don't overthink it.
Zhi must miss Chen Luzhou a lot.
But she doesn't
want to contact him actively.
That's why she asked you out
to catch up.
That's it.
True.
However, in my opinion,
they'll make up eventually.
Although both Zhi and Lucy
look carefree on the surface,
actually
they haven't let go at all.
Look, I've worked out quite well, right?
Look at my biceps.
Stylish Zhu, move aside a bit.
Let me see the one behind you.
Right.
Fine.
Not bad.
Bye, I need to train.
- Bye.
- Why hang up?
Hey.
Zhi.
Let's go.
This place is really good.
I booked a private room.
Here.
Hello, this way please.
I'm starving.
Let me see the menu.
Here.
Okay.
Thank you.
Trust me.
One sashimi platter, please.
And then two eel rice bowls, please.
Alright.
Please wait a moment.
You've been working out?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm not bragging.
Others work out for a year
and still can't reach my level.
It took me only a month
to undergo a new transformation.
See that?
Yes.
Well...
Can you change back?
The way you are now is a bit
too much.
Too...
Why is that?
Even Cai Yingying said
that guys with pecs
make her feel secure.
Here's the thing.
The standard
for guys and girls about muscles
are different.
We like the kind
that looks slim in clothes
yet defined naked.
It seems most girls don't like it when
a guy's chest is bigger than theirs.
They find it quite unattractive.
Then I
shouldn't bulk up.
I need to lost weight.
Waiter,
cancel the eel rice.
Alright.
Thank you.
Do you miss him?
I got your message yesterday,
and knew you somewhat missed him.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
have reached out to me.
Thank you.
This is quite strong.
Come quickly!
Why?
Try it.
Try what?
Here you go.
What's this?
This is my grandma's
homemade liquor, look.
It's very tasty.
Drinking in broad daylight?
You know what?
Dad won't even let
Mr. Cai have a sip.
I stole it, so give it a try.
Is it good?
You...
Are you messing with me?
Don't pinch my face.
If it swells up, then it's your fault.
Fine, my fault.
You dare talk about responsibility.
You take responsibility
for kissing me that much?
I don't have to.
Why not?
Because I said so.
You take a sip. It's not good.
Actually,
I've been in Beijing this long,
but I'm hesitant to contact you.
Mainly, I'm afraid
you'll think of him when you see me.
Why are you staring at me like that?
See if I can remember him.
I heard there's a handsome guy
named Jiang Yu.
Is he as handsome as me?
How do you know Jiang Yu?
I have informants.
How many informants
did Chen Luzhou deploy around me?
Did he ask you to spy on me?
Your dishes.
No.
When your grades came out,
he knew you'd go to Huaguang.
So, he asked me
to keep an eye on you,
lest you be bullied.
It's not spying.
So, how exactly is Jiang Yu?
Is he as handsome as Lucy?
What exactly does he mean?
Xu Zhi, don't take me wrong.
He doesn't mean anything.
He really just wanted me
to keep an eye on you.
He's just afraid you'll be bullied.
He also said
you could even date other people.
Xu Zhi,
let me tell you.
I think,
constantly looking
for his shadow in others
really isn't good.
Why not
try getting into a relationship?
After all, Lucy is abroad,
and won't be back soon.
I think you
can't keep dragging it out like this.
You're right.
Where's Mr. Handsome?
Where?
There.
Which one?
Over there.
- He's really handsome.
- Cute.
He's so handsome.
If models were like this,
then I'd come to art class every day.
When did he arrive?
Really handsome.
You're finally here.
You're back this soon.
Are you back as a model?
No.
They said this is your spot.
So, I was waiting here.
So handsome.
He isn't a model.
This is my bro, Lucy.
He finally came back
from Europe to see me.
Since you're here, let's go eat.
But you have class.
You're more important.
He left.
Better at drawing?
Tell me about it.
Not a model?
I haven't seen enough yet.
Aren't you working out?
Have some meat
to gain weight.
I don't need to gain weight.
I need to lose weight.
I have to eat greens.
You're losing weight eating skewers?
What else then?
Eat salad every day?
How bland that is.
Just like today's lunch.
The Japanese food Xu Zhi and I ate was
so expensive and yet tasteless.
You haven't seen Xu Zhi yet, have you?
She didn't mention you earlier.
I went to Huaguang University.
But I didn't tell her.
Why not?
I took the waitlist admission test.
But the results are not out yet.
Before the results are confirmed,
I don't want her to know.
Waitlist admission?
You don't have to leave then?
Nice.
Hold on.
Did your family agree?
Didn't you always say
I was a mama's boy?
From today on, I'll listen to no one
but myself.
Nice.
Good for you.
Right now,
you dare to say no to your mom.
That's how it should be.
Bro, give me a hug.
You're crazy.
Come on.
Get off.
Wait a minute, you...
Got some girl stuff after going abroad?
What's this?
Why do you care?
Is it Xu Zhi's?
Lucy.
You're not a mama's boy now.
You're lovesick.
Anyway,
my return must be kept a secret.
Don't let it slip to Cai Yingying.
Lucy.
As for Xu Zhi, I can keep it secret.
However,
I think you living alone
is a bit too lonely.
Here.
I'll stay with you.
We can chat
like we used to.
Alright, it's just that...
My roommate
really drives me crazy.
He doesn't shower
or wash his feet every day.
He has smelly feet,
and puts it near my head.
I can't stand it.
I'm almost breaking down.
We split the utility bills.
Come on, eat up.
It's on me, alright?
Waiter,
more dishes.
Alright.
Come on.
See what more you'd like to eat.
Xu Zhi, how is it?
Isn't it just a class?
This is Professor Wang's class.
Many people fail calculus each year.
You never know.
This might
hold me back from graduating.
I want to give him a good impression.
I think it's unlikely.
You look like you're selling insurance.
Xu Zhi.
I'm going to be angry.
It's Professor Wang's class.
You two still dare to be late?
In our freshman year,
we wouldn't even eat lunch.
We'd go straight
to the classroom and wait.
Professor Wang is that harsh?
Wang is a man of character.
Unless you are really capable,
you don't need him for
the key points for the final exam.
Otherwise, watch your attitude.
He might just fail you directly.
Let's hurry up, don't be late.
Go, quickly!
Run faster.
If Xu Zhi is asked
for WeChat on the way,
you'll be late for sure.
Go.
Jiang Yu asked me to save seats for you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Senior Jiang Yu?
When were you guys a thing?
You didn't even tell me.
Tell your boyfriend
to save a seat in the front row.
Impression points, you know.
He's not my boyfriend.
Next time, let's come earlier.
Sorry, I couldn't save seats.
It's okay.
Class begin.
Hello, guys.
Hello, sir.
Please open to page 27 of the book.
This question...
Xu Gongzhu,
please answer this question.
Same order but not equivalent,
infinitesimal.
That's right.
This is the topic
we need to learn this class.
It seems some students
have done their preparation carefully.
In my class,
I hope everyone will prepare diligently.
Please sit down.
I'll definitely fail.
Will I not be able to graduate?
It's okay if you
don't know the prep material.
Do you know it then?
Figures.
I heard other departments
have additional enrollment slots.
They've missed
a month's worth of classes.
I'm afraid everyone will pass,
except me.
That won't do.
No.
I must pass.
I can't fail.
I'm begging.
You can do it.
He definitely remembers me.
What should I do?
Lift your foot.
No, your butt.
You might as well get up.
Alright.
What's this?
Lucky color.
You'll definitely make it.
(College Entrance Examination Results)
Wait.
There's something.
Everything goes well.
Hold on a moment.
There's another thing.
May all your wishes come true.
Is there more?
If not, I'm going to check.
Go ahead.
How is it?
How is it? Tell me!
Say something!
No good?
Impossible.
(Successful)
You made it.
I'm more nervous
checking your grades than my own.
Stop with this in the future, Lucy.
My heart can't take it.
You can finally tell Zhi now.
No rush.
Let me finish my current work first.
You got into Huaguang University, bro.
Why are you still working?
Let's go have a good meal to celebrate.
I got into Huaguang University.
Will you pay my tuition?
Oh, right.
I won't be back this noon.
You handle lunch yourself.
Alright.
Then take care, bye.
Okay.
To challenge Her Majesty,
you're actually supporting yourself.
Even paying your college fee.
Lucy, oh Lucy,
you're simply too impressive.
Hurry.
Be careful.
Go.
Oh, my gosh,
raining this hard?
This weather changes.
Such terrible weather.
I'm all wet.
Where's my phone?
Good that it's raining.
The client wants a shot
of the mountain lodge.
Who'll go for it?
A 500 bonus for one shot.
Only 500?
500 for a shot?
Must go to the mountain top.
It's slippery.
It won't cover the medical expenses.
- Should be 5,000.
- Yeah.
500 for one shot.
That's too cheap.
I'll go.
Eager to show off this young.
- Exactly.
- Can you believe it?
What's he after?
He looks like a rich kid.
See his clothes?
Exactly.
They're all designer brands.
He even competes for 500.
He's here for the thrill.
500 can't cover dry-cleaning.
Yeah.
Interested in joining
the student council?
With a personality like yours,
you'd be perfect for the presidency.
When departments start to fight,
someone needs to oversee the situation.
You can definitely
handle it.
Forget it.
We've been having late night meetings.
My head hurts.
There isn't any important work.
I still have to report daily.
Too formalistic.
I wouldn't have joined any department.
Alright.
What's up?
Not doing anything.
Snatching people for you.
Why are you avoiding me?
You stepped on my shadow.
Okay.
I'll walk behind you.
Now you step on me.
I have something to do, bye.
Are you going home
for National Day?
Do you need me for any work?
There's something.
It's fine if you go home.
It's just after the holiday,
the competition arrangements
haven't been settled yet.
Basketball and photography contests.
Art exhibitions and more.
Our posters are outdated.
There are some edits
that are not yet completed.
If you're not going home,
I'd like you to work overtime.
Is that okay?
Then leave the key with me.
I'll join you.
After that,
I'll take you to a concert.
No.
My bestie is visiting.
I have to stay with her.
Probably can't work.
What about the concert then?
Actually, Senior,
I added you on WeChat
because your profile picture
looks like a friend of mine.
I thought it was him.
Also, I don't intend to date.
Profile picture?
Is it your ex-boyfriend
from high school?
Yes.
What kind of person is he?
You still haven't blacklisted him.
He's a punk.
Your new Beijing number.
Where did you buy it?
There's a business office
next to No.2 canteen.
How much left?
Gonna finish it tonight?
I have to pull an all-nighter
and finish it.
Our department has a lot of chores.
I can't even study.
No worries, I'm with you.
We'll fight till dawn.
It shouldn't be that serious.
You're spreading anxiety.
What do you know?
Late-night snacks are the best.
Come on, cheers.
Cheers!
Keep it up!
(Today's Media)
Send this to Finance.
Hello, boss.
Not bad.
Caught on quickly.
Thanks to you for this shoot.
Everyone, take a look.
Chen is already leaving
but still works diligently.
If everyone could be like him,
then our company
would grow strong.
- Yes, boss.
Chen.
The company lacks talents like you.
You're welcome to come back.
For future outsourcing gigs,
you'll be my No.1 option.
Thank you, boss.
You need to pay me
for this project.
And my bonus, 500.
Absolutely.
Thank you.
♪We are not afraid of
the complicated world♪
♪Only passionate love
like a ray of sunshine♪
♪Can beat the night♪
♪We can outrun time♪
♪Let beautiful stories and wishes♪
♪All blend into our season♪
♪When the summer breeze blows♪
♪We don't think about the fallen leaves♪
♪Just want to remember this moment♪
♪With you, I actually
start looking forward to rainy days♪
♪You are like an umbrella,
always catching the raindrops♪
♪We are not afraid of
the complicated world♪
♪Only passionate love
like a ray of sunshine♪
♪All blend into our season♪
♪The cicadas' chirping
seems to never cease♪
♪The years we have spent♪
♪Also seem to have no end♪
♪Only you know everything about me,
no words needed♪
♪My equation,
you always have the solution♪
♪We are not afraid of
the complicated world♪
♪Only passionate love
like a ray of sunshine♪
♪Can beat the night♪
♪We can outrun time♪
♪Let beautiful stories and wishes♪
♪All blend into our season♪
♪No matter how the future changes♪
Good morning.
Hello.
One meat bun and soy milk.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
♪We'll turn our backs
on youth together and take risks♪
♪Let all the sadness and joy♪
♪All blend into our season♪
♪Make you forget all your rules♪
Who is it?
Disturbing people this early.
I'll call the police to arrest you.
Surprise!
Happy to see me?
Help me carry this.
I...
I'm exhausted.
Wait.
How did you know about here?
Did you forget the admission brochure
you sent me?
Zhu, this is not bad.
This time I came to Beijing
for training.
I deliberately didn't tell you.
It's a surprise.
It is quite a surprise.
Quickly call Xu Zhi over.
I'll pretend to do delivery
and surprise her.
Call her here?
No.
Why not?
I said no.
What's wrong?
Drink some water, come on.
Two cups of instant noodles.
Come on.
You're in a relationship?
You!
No, this...
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
No.
It's inappropriate for me to be here.
Not at all.
Your girlfriend is back.
Not my...
Hurry up.
Why not lock the door, Zhu Yangqi?
Up so early today?
Chen Luzhou.
Cai Yingying?
Aren't you supposed to be abroad?
Don't tell Xu Zhi
that Lucy came back to Beijing.
How could that be possible?
Sisterhood comes before anything.
There are no secrets between us.
Cai Yingying.
Don't call her yet.
I'll tell her when the time is right.
Fine.
Then you better hurry up.
I can't hold it in long.
Thanks.
Since I did you a favor,
you help me with one too.
Me?
Sure.
I...
Thanks.
So you ask me out for no reason?
Of course.
You treated me last time.
It's my turn now.
Can I have a hug?
Give a hug.
Just give a hug.
You hug.
I'll hug.
Are you okay?
You okay?
Zhi.
Yingying.
That hurts.
Stop it.
Went all this way to surprise a friend,
only to be horribly rejected.
Tell me, can I not feel hurt?
Let's go eat.
Let's go.
Wait for me.
I'm still here.
Zhi, you have no idea.
Repeating these classes
is simply unbearable.
It's harder than senior year.
Really?
Weren't you quite happy in senior year?
You really know how to chat.
Did I ever tell you
that Tan Xu and I are classmates?
How's he doing?
Not so well.
He didn't do well in the last mock exam.
His parents hurried to school
and scolded him,
saying he's worthless.
So, his gaslighting
runs in the family?
So, you know,
people who are hateful are pathetic.
Does it still hurt?
It's much better now.
I twisted my ankle the other day.
My roommate brought me
a large bag of medicine.
She didn't know who sent it.
There were a lot
of arthritis medicines inside.
I was thinking,
besides you and Dad, the only person
who knows about this is Chen Luzhou.
I thought he had gone back to Beijing.
I went looking in the rain.
Zhi, actually...
(Snitch.)
Actually, what?
Actually, I saw a saying online.
No matter
how far apart we are,
we'll meet as we expected.
So, you and Chen Luzhou
will definitely meet again.
I never said I wanted to see him.
By the way,
I'll text you my new number.
You've changed your number?
Didn't you say that you
were worried Luzhou would call you?
That's why
you never changed your number.
Done.
Nowadays,
it's easy to contact someone
if you want to.
What do you mean?
You didn't give Chen Luzhou
your new number?
No.
There's no need, right?
It's okay.
(Tell Chen Luzhou to hurry up.)
(Zhi is ready to move on.)
Zhao Tianqi.
Tianqi, let's go eat.
He's not here.
Hey, you...
Chen Luzhou!
Ke.
You...
What are you doing here?
I live here.
You, I...
- I...
- You also live here?
What's going on?
I didn't expect to see you this soon.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I participated
in the waitlist admission test.
Public Administration.
Doesn't matter.
With your brain, you'll do great.
Wait a minute.
You.
You came here without telling me?
Unbelievable.
My bad.
Have you eaten?
I need to tidy up first.
Tidy up for what? Let's go.
Soon there'll be nothing.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
(Reporting to Zhi,
here at the training school.)
Okay, we'll meet
during the National Day holiday.
On the way to the No.2 canteen,
many people were sizing him up.
Super handsome.
- Xu Zhi.
Come quick.
Me and Liu Yisi
saw a handsome guy.
Huh?
How handsome is he?
- Very.
- Extremely handsome.
All the girls outside the canteen
were secretly checking him up.
That Foreign Languages girl
even asked for his number.
I heard he's from Public Administration.
We'll be attending
Professor Wang's class together!
The class will be a big hit.
You two are so infatuated.
Don't forget to study,
or you won't graduate.
Einstein once said
admiring handsome guys is good for you.
That is very good for studying.
Really.
You haven't eaten yet?
Have a meeting later.
Go to No.2 canteen.
He should be eating there.
No.2 canteen is good.
It has pig's trotters rice.
Forget that!
The cute guy's there!
Really.
Such a face is wasted.
So dense.
This is delicious.
There's a line every day.
Okay.
We'll be late.
Xu Zhi.
♪Listen to the cicadas in the midsummer♪
Coming.
♪The reflection in your eyes♪
♪A brilliant scenery♪
♪Moonlight spills over
the endless clear sky♪
♪The roar of the heartbeat♪
♪Drew a trajectory♪
♪Crush, when night meets dawn♪
♪Crush, rushing to you in the crowd♪
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
♪Fervent, boiling love♪
♪How you long for the future♪
♪Charging recklessly, getting hurt♪
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
♪If tears fill your eyes♪
♪Let the damp wind stay in memories♪
♪We stand by each other among the crowd♪
♪The endless clear sky
disperses the rainy season♪
♪Taking away all the mud♪
♪Leaving an echo♪
Is this good?
♪Baby, fall in my heart♪
♪You're the only one♪
Don't recognize me?
What's your relationship with Luzhou?
His older brother.
Chen Sanzhou.
Alright.
Then let's keep our distance.
After all, he's still in Europe.
Xu Zhi.
(What kind of person is he?)
(He's a punk.)
♪Like a cloud drifting away♪
♪Freely crossing the vast sky♪
♪The world is too quiet♪
♪Amplifying all the sounds♪
♪Who will visit me♪
♪Treading carefully
into my personal space♪
♪Turning the frozen loneliness♪
♪Into concern and care♪
♪Watching stars rise and fall♪
♪Gently pushing me to tour your world♪
♪Swirling into a vortex♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪The lonely clock♪
♪A relentless pursuit, day and night♪
♪Are we both♪
♪Attracted to each other♪
♪Falling into you♪
♪You are the whirlwind
changing the course of our future♪
♪Just a few more embraces away♪
♪From reaching eternity♪
♪After rushing recklessly♪
♪We approach each other♪
♪Without turning back♪
♪In your eyes, I see myself♪
♪Falling into you♪